RAJESH EDAYANGAT

(91) - 8157836809

rajeshedayangat@gmail.com

http://www.rajeshedayangat.tech/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rajesh-edayangatt-4a3a1010b/

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a software engineer with 3 years of professional working experience. My major expertise is on web application development. I love to learn and work with new technologies as well. Currently, I'm working as a Software Engineer developing e commerce and erp softwares. Strong experience with php, javascript and html.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Story Box Communication Pvt Ltd, Ernakulam, September 2018 - Present

Software Engineer

- Integration of user-facing elements developed by front-end developers
- > Build efficient, testable, and reusable PHP modules
- > Integration of data storage
- > Developing new erp modules for the erp web application

Netstager Technologies, Calicut, May 2017 - Sep 2018

Software Engineer

- ➤ Building PHP websites using PHP based frameworks like ecommerces , tavel booking applications.
- Document and maintain software functionality
- Developing advanced database driven websites & systems including eCommerce
- Developing 3D rendering applications

Genius Group Of Global ,Calicut, Dec 2016 - May 2017

Software Engineer

- Building PHP websites using PHP based frameworks.
- Building new modules for the hrms application and certificate tracking application
- Developing advanced database driven websites & systems including eCommerce

Brahmasuthra Technologies ,Calicut, Apr 2016 - Dec 2016

Software Intern

- Building PHP websites using PHP based frameworks.
- Helping senior developers to building different php modules and front end development

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Application, Bharathiar University Coimbatore in year 2014.

SKILLS

- > PHP , LARAVEL AND CODEIGNITER
- > MYSQL
- > HTML, CSS
- > JAVSCRIPT , JQUERY AND THREE JS
- REACT AND REDUX (BASIC)
- > NODE JS WITH EXPRESS MONGODB (BASIC)